Antonio Pavicevac-Ortiz

Web Developer

PROFILE

My journey began as an aspiring Illustrator but soon was reforged into a career as a Graphic Designer with the Web playing a supporting role.

However during the last 4+ years, I have moved into the Web Development industry fulltime! It encomposes a combination of formalized learning as well as being self taught. My area of concentration is JavaScript. I love projects which distill design, data and purpose to create something dynamic and fun!

SKILLS

- JavaScript* Node* Express* React* Redux*
- NextJS* PassportJS* Webpack* MongoDB Atlas*
- MongooseJS* JQuery Sequelize HTML5 Semantic UI React*
- CSS* SASS* Bootstrap Git NPM
- Shopify API's, Liquid SalesForce API's
- * Software used with HillFinder

EXPERIENCE

August 2018 - Present

Revlon Inc.

- Augmented site front-end using (JavaScript and jQuery) to enhance UX based on changing business gaols and needs
- Part of team which maintained two (Almay.com and Revlon.com) sites using Vue.js .NET and Sitecore CMS
- Utilized Shopify platform to relaunch/port existing website in mobile-first approach and strategy
- Worked with Analytics team in regards to configuring GTM and GA for custom Shopify Instance
- Integrated various private apps, API's (Elavar, Criterio) on Shopify platform
- Ensured sites met ADA compliance, SEO performant
- Managed 3 sites on SaleForce/SiteGenesis/demandware

April 2019 - Present

HillFinder

This is an idea for a web-app I had during a hackathon, at FullStack Academy. It uses Geolocation API's to find user requests based on declining elevations. I am building it with NextJS—a React framework because I want offline capabilities, Check it out!

November 2012 -Febraury 2017

Avon Inc.

- Integrated JavaScript/jQuery on representative website to enhance user experience and increase reproduit
- Developed a script to automate the output of a weekly newsletter which saved hours towards implementation
- Developed W3C websites using standard compliant HTML5 and CSS3 (SCSS) and JavaScript
- Tested websites for cross browser compatibility using tools such as Browserstack
- Collaborated with E-mail Marketing Team to code, conceptualize and execute marketing email campaigns

CONTACTS

69-10 213th street, Oakland Gardens, NY 11364

917,679,6827

17antonio.ortiz@gmail.com https://www.antonio-p-ortiz.com github linkedin stackoverflow

EDUCATION

Full Stack Academy/Certificate

February 2018

• Immersive 3 month program centered around JavaScript on the Front and Back end.

Fashion Institute of Technology

/Bachelor of Fine Arts

New York City

• Majored in Illustration; Minor in Graphic Design

ABOUT ME

Aside from web development, I really love to run, meditate and cook.

I'm a generalist at heart, and you've probably heard of the saying "Jack of all trades master of none", but recently I heard an addendum to it, "Ahh, but still to be better than a master of one"!